<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:fn="http://www.w3.org/2005/xpath-functions" xmlns:xdt="http://www.w3.org/2005/xpath-datatypes"><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>U.S. Department of Commerce, U.S. Census Bureau, Geography Division</origin><origin>NJ Office of Information Technology (NJOIT), Office of Geographic Information Systems (OGIS)</origin><pubdate>2013</pubdate><title>TIGER/Line Shapefile, 2010, 2010 state, New Jersey, 2010 Census  Block State-based, NAD83 NJ State Plane feet</title><geoform>vector digital data</geoform><pubinfo><pubplace>Trenton, NJ</pubplace><publish>NJ Office of Information Technology (NJOIT), Office of Geographic Information Systems (OGIS)</publish></pubinfo><onlink>https://njgin.state.nj.us/oit/gis/download/Census2010Blk.zip</onlink><onlink> http://www.census.gov/geo/www/tiger</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>
Most of the content below was provided by the U.S. Census Bureau. Original TIGER metadata have been edited to reflect data projection and redistribution by the State of New Jersey.

Census Blocks are statistical areas bounded on all sides by visible features, such as streets, roads, streams, and railroad tracks, and/or by nonvisible boundaries such as city, town, township, and county limits, and short line-of-sight extensions of streets and roads.  Census blocks are relatively small in area; for example, a block in a city bounded by streets.  However, census blocks in remote areas are often large and irregular and may even be many square miles in area.
</abstract><purpose>In order for others to use the information in the Census MAF/TIGER database in a geographic information system (GIS) or for other geographic applications, the Census Bureau releases to the public extracts of the database in the form of TIGER/Line Shapefiles.</purpose><supplinf>
Attribute GEOID10 can be used to join census 2010 data at the appropriate summary level.

Attributes for 100% Population and 100% Housing Units from Redistricting data have been added to these records by joining to an extract from the Geo Header table.

The TIGER/Line Files are shapefiles and related database files (.dbf) that are an extract of selected geographic and cartographic information from the U.S. Census Bureau's Master Address File / Topologically Integrated Geographic Encoding and Referencing (MAF/TIGER) Database (MTDB).  The MTDB represents a seamless national file with no overlaps or gaps between parts, however, each TIGER/Line File is designed to stand alone as an independent data set, or they can be combined to cover the entire nation.  Census Blocks are statistical areas bounded on all sides by visible features, such as streets, roads, streams, and railroad tracks, and/or by nonvisible boundaries such as city, town, township, and county limits, and short line-of-sight extensions of streets and roads.  Census blocks are relatively small in area; for example, a block in a city bounded by streets.  However, census blocks in remote areas are often large and irregular and may even be many square miles in area.  A common misunderstanding is that data users think census blocks are used geographically to build all other census geographic areas, rather all other census geographic areas are updated and then used as the primary constraints, along with roads and water features, to delineate the tabulation blocks.  As a result, all 2010 Census blocks nest within every other 2010 Census geographic area, so that Census Bureau statistical data can be tabulated at the block level and aggregated up to the appropriate geographic areas.  Census blocks cover all territory in the United States, Puerto Rico, and the Island Areas (American Samoa, Guam, the Commonwealth of the Northern Mariana Islands, and the U.S. Virgin Islands).  Blocks are the smallest geographic areas for which the Census Bureau publishes data from the decennial census.  A block may consist of one or more faces.
</supplinf></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>201001</begdate><enddate>201102</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date of data by U.S. Census Bureau</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>None planned</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-75.563586</westbc><eastbc>-73.88506</eastbc><northbc>41.357423</northbc><southbc>38.788657</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Categories</themekt><themekey>boundaries</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>State or equivalent entity</themekey><themekey>Polygon</themekey><themekey>Block</themekey><themekey>Census Block</themekey></theme><place><placekt>INCITS.38-200x (R2004),INCITS.31-200x (R2007),INCITS.454-200x,INCITS 455-200x,INCITS 446-2008</placekt><placekey>United States</placekey><placekey>U.S.</placekey><placekey>State or Equivalent Entity</placekey><placekey>New Jersey</placekey><placekey>NJ</placekey><placekey>34</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>None</accconst><useconst>See Purpose and Data Quality sections for conditions that limit appropriate uses.

Acknowledgement of the data set providers would be appreciated for maps, data or other products derived from this data set.

The TIGER/Line Shapefile products are not copyrighted however TIGER/Line and Census TIGER are registered trademarks of the U.S. Census Bureau.  These products are free to use in a product or publication, however acknowledgement must be given to the U.S. Census Bureau as the source.

The boundary information in the TIGER/Line Shapefiles are for statistical data collection and tabulation purposes only; their depiction and designation for statistical purposes does not constitute a determination of jurisdictional authority or rights of ownership or entitlement and they are not legal land descriptions.Coordinates in the TIGER/Line shapefiles have six implied decimal places, but the positional accuracy of these coordinates is not as great as the six decimal places suggest.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>U.S. Department of Commerce, U.S. Census Bureau, Geography Division, Geographic Products Branch</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing address</addrtype><address>4600 Silver Hill Road, Stop 7400</address><city>Washington</city><state>DC</state><postal>20233-7400</postal><country>United States</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>301-763-1128</cntvoice><cntfax>301-763-4710</cntfax><cntemail>geo.tiger@census.gov</cntemail><cntinst>Use this contact for questions about content of the original (non-projected) data as released by the U.S. Census Bureau.</cntinst></cntinfo></ptcontac><native>Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 3; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.2.4.1420</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>
Accurate against Federal Information Processing Standards (FIPS), FIPS Publication 6-4, and FIPS-55 at the 100% level for the codes and base names.  The remaining attribute information has been examined but has not been fully tested for accuracy.

No attribute checking was performed by NJ after the join of Census count data.
</attraccr></attracc><logic>
The Census Bureau performed automated tests to ensure logical consistency and limits of shapefiles.  Segments making up the outer and inner boundaries of a polygon tie end-to-end to completely enclose the area.  All polygons are tested for closure.

The Census Bureau uses its internally developed geographic update system to enhance and modify spatial and attribute data in the Census MAF/TIGER database.  Standard geographic codes, such as FIPS codes for states, counties, municipalities, county subdivisions, places, American Indian/Alaska Native/Native Hawaiian areas, and congressional districts are used when encoding spatial entities.  The Census Bureau performed spatial data tests for logical consistency of the codes during the compilation of the original Census MAF/TIGER database files.  Most of the codes for geographic entities except states, counties, urban areas, Core Based Statistical Areas (CBSAs), American Indian Areas (AIAs), and congressional districts were provided to the Census Bureau by the USGS, the agency responsible for maintaining FIPS 55.  Feature attribute information has been examined but has not been fully tested for consistency.

For the TIGER/Line Shapefiles, the Point and Vector Object Count for the G-polygon SDTS Point and Vector Object Type reflects the number of records in the shapefile attribute table.  For multi-polygon features, only one attribute record exists for each multi-polygon rather than one attribute record per individual G-polygon component of the multi-polygon feature.  TIGER/Line Shapefile multi-polygons are an exception to the G-polygon object type classification.  Therefore, when multi-polygons exist in a shapefile, the object count will be less than the actual number of G-polygons.

No further checking done by New Jersey.
</logic><complete>Data completeness of the TIGER/Line Shapefiles reflects the contents of the Census MAF/TIGER database at the time the TIGER/Line Shapefiles were created.</complete><lineage><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><origin>U.S. Department of Commerce, U.S. Census Bureau, Geography Division</origin><pubdate>Unpublished material</pubdate><title>Census MAF/TIGER database</title></citeinfo></srccite><typesrc>online</typesrc><srctime><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>201001</begdate><enddate>201007</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><srccurr>publication date</srccurr></srctime><srccitea>MAF/TIGER</srccitea><srccontr>The selected geographic and cartographic information (line segments) are derived from the U.S. Census Bureau's Master Address File Topologically Integrated Geographic Encoding and Referencing (MAF/TIGER) database.</srccontr></srcinfo><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><origin>U.S. Census Bureau</origin><pubdate>201102</pubdate><title>February 2011 NJ Census 2010 Redistricting Data P.L. 94-171</title><geoform>tabular digital data</geoform><pubinfo><pubplace>Suitland, MD</pubplace><publish>U.S. Census Bureau</publish></pubinfo><onlink>http://www2.census.gov/census_2010/01-Redistricting_File--PL_94-171/New_Jersey/</onlink></citeinfo></srccite><typesrc>computer program</typesrc><srctime><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>201102</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo><srccurr>publication date</srccurr></srctime><srccitea>Census 2010 Redistricting GEO HEADER table</srccitea><srccontr>Values for total population and housing unit counts</srccontr></srcinfo><procstep><procdesc>TIGER/Line Shapefiles are extracted from the Census MAF/TIGER database by nation, state, county, and entity.  Census MAF/TIGER data for all of the aforementioned geographic entities are then distributed among the shapefiles each containing attributes for line, polygon, or landmark geographic data.</procdesc><srcused>Census MAF/TIGER</srcused><procdate>2010</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>
Shapefiles received from the NJ State Data Center (NJ Dept of Labor) were projected to NAD83 NJ State Plane feet and exported to NJOIT spatial data server. 

Population and Housing Unit count data and codes for census blocks were extracted from the Redistricting Data for NJ released in early February. These data were joined to the TIGER census block geography on GEOID and the count attributes added to the census block records.

Edits were made to metadata.
</procdesc><srcused>tl_2010_34_tabblock10.shp</srcused><srcused>Census 2010 Redistricting GEO HEADER table</srcused><procdate>201102010</procdate><srcprod>tl_2010_34_tabblock10_SP.shp</srcprod><srcprod>OGIS.TIGER2010_BLK</srcprod><proccont><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>NJOIT OGIS</cntorg><cntper>Yelena Pikovskaya, Edith Konopka</cntper></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing address</addrtype><address>PO Box 212</address><city>Trenton</city><state>NJ</state><postal>08625-0212</postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>609.777.3774</cntvoice><cntemail>edith.konopka@oit.state.nj.us</cntemail><hours>9-4</hours><cntinst>Email is preferred</cntinst></cntinfo></proccont></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Layer re-exported to shapefile and metadata edited.</procdesc><procdate>20130719</procdate><proccont><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>NJOIT OGIS</cntorg><cntper>Edith Konopka</cntper></cntorgp><cntemail>edith.konopka@oit.state.nj.us</cntemail></cntinfo></proccont></procstep></lineage></dataqual><spdoinfo><indspref>Federal Information Processing Standards (FIPS), ANSI, and feature names.</indspref><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><spref><horizsys><planar><gridsys><gridsysn>State Plane Coordinate System 1983</gridsysn><spcs><spcszone>2900</spcszone><transmer><sfctrmer>0.999900</sfctrmer><longcm>-74.500000</longcm><latprjo>38.833333</latprjo><feast>492125.000000</feast><fnorth>0.000000</fnorth></transmer></spcs></gridsys><planci><plance>coordinate pair</plance><coordrep><absres>0.000328</absres><ordres>0.000328</ordres></coordrep><plandu>survey feet</plandu></planci></planar><geodetic><horizdn>North American Datum of 1983 in the 48 contiguous states, the District of Columbia, Alaska, Hawaii, Puerto Rico, the Virgin Islands of the United States, and the Pacific Island Areas.</horizdn><ellips>Geodetic Reference System 80</ellips><semiaxis>6378137</semiaxis><denflat>298257</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>Govt_TIGER2010_blk.shp</enttypl><enttypd>2010 Census Block State-based</enttypd><enttypds>U.S. Census Bureau</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>FID</attrlabl><attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>STATEFP10</attrlabl><attrdef>
2010 Census state Federal Information Processing Standards
                 (FIPS) codes
</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><codesetd><codesetn>
INCITS.38-200x (R2004), Codes for the Identification of
                      the States, the District of Columbia, Puerto Rico, and the
                      Insular Areas of the United States (Formerly FIPS 5-2)
</codesetn><codesets>U.S. Census Bureau</codesets></codesetd></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>COUNTYFP10</attrlabl><attrdef>
2010 Census county Federal Information Processing Standards
                 (FIPS) code
</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><codesetd><codesetn>
INCITS.31-200x (R2007), Codes for the Identification of
                      the Counties and Equivalent Areas of the United States,
                      Puerto Rico, and the Insular Areas of the United States
                      (Formerly FIPS 6-4)
</codesetn><codesets>U.S. Census Bureau</codesets></codesetd></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRACTCE10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census census tract code</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>000000</edomv><edomvd>
Water tract in some coastal and Great Lakes water and
                    territorial sea
</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census</edomvds></edom><edom><edomv>000100 to 998999</edomv><edomvd>Census tract number</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BLOCKCE10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census tabulation block number</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>0001 to 9999</edomv><edomvd>tabulation block number</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>GEOID10</attrlabl><attrdef>
Block identifier; a concatenation of 2010 Census state Federal
                 Information Processing Standards (FIPS) code, county FIPS code,
                 census tract code, and tabulation block number
</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><codesetd><codesetn>
INCITS.38-200x (R2004), Codes for the Identification of
                      the States, the District of Columbia, Puerto Rico, and the
                      Insular Areas of the United States (Formerly FIPS 5-2),
                      INCITS.31-200x (R2007), Codes for the Identification of
                      the Counties and Equivalent Areas of the United States,
                      Puerto Rico, and the Insular Areas of the United States
                      (Formerly FIPS 6-4), the census tract code that appears in
                      TRACTCE10 and the tabulation block number that appears in
                      BLOCKCE10
</codesetn><codesets>U.S. Census Bureau</codesets></codesetd></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NAME10</attrlabl><attrdef>
2010 Census tabulation block name; a concatenation of "Block",
                 and the current tabulation block number
</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Refer to the tabulation block number that appears in BLOCKCE10</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>MTFCC10</attrlabl><attrdef>MAF/TIGER feature class code</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>G5040</edomv><edomvd>Tabulation Block</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>UR10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census urban/rural indicator</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>M</edomv><edomvd>
Mixed - part of the land area is classified as urban and
                    part is classified as rural
</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>Not Applicable (water-only and international areas)</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom><edom><edomv>R</edomv><edomvd>Area is classified as rural</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom><edom><edomv>U</edomv><edomvd>Area is classified as urban</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>UACE10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census urban area code</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>00001 to 98999</edomv><edomvd>Urban Area Code</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>FUNCSTAT10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census functional status</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>S</edomv><edomvd>Statistical entity</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ALAND10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census land area (square meters)</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>0 to 9,999,999,999,999</edomv><edomvd>Blank</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>AWATER10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census water area (square meters)</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>0 to 9,999,999,999,999</edomv><edomvd>Blank</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>INTPTLAT10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census latitude of the internal point</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>00</edomv><edomvd>Blank</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>INTPTLON10</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 Census longitude of the internal point</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>00</edomv><edomvd>Blank</edomvd><edomvds>U.S. Census Bureau</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SHAPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef><attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>HH100_RD</attrlabl></attr><attr><attrlabl>POP100_RD</attrlabl><attrdef>2010 census 100% population count for the block, from Redistricting File PL_94-171, Table PL_GEOHD_2010, POP100</attrdef><attrdefs>U.S. Census Bureau</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>0</rdommin><rdommax>4665</rdommax><attrunit>human person</attrunit><attrmres>1</attrmres></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SHAPE_AREA</attrlabl><attrdef>Area of feature in internal units squared.</attrdef><attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SHAPE_LEN</attrlabl><attrdef>Perimeter of the feature in internal units</attrdef><attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>U.S. Department of Commerce, U.S. Census Bureau, Geography Division, Geographic Products Branch</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing address</addrtype><address>4600 Silver Hill Road, Stop 7400</address><city>Washington</city><state>DC</state><postal>20233-7400</postal><country>United States</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>301-763-1128</cntvoice><cntfax>301-763-4710</cntfax><cntemail>geo.tiger@census.gov</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>Downloadable Data</resdesc><distliab>No warranty, expressed or implied is made with regard to the accuracy of these data, and no liability is assumed by the U.S. Government in general or the U.S. Census Bureau in specific as to the spatial or attribute accuracy of the data.  The act of distribution shall not constitute any such warranty and no responsibility is assumed by the U.S. government in the use of these files.  The boundary information in the TIGER/Line Shapefiles is for statistical data collection and tabulation purposes only; their depiction and designation for statistical purposes do not constitute a determination of jurisdictional authority or rights of ownership or entitlement and they are not legal land descriptions.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>TGRSHP (compressed)</formname><filedec>PK-ZIP, version 1.93 A or higher</filedec></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>http://www.census.gov/geo/www/tiger</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt><offoptn><offmedia>DVD-ROM (Only if offered offline)</offmedia><recfmt>ISO 9660</recfmt></offoptn></digtopt></digform><fees>The online copy of the TIGER/Line files may be accessed without charge.</fees><ordering>To obtain more information about ordering TIGER/Line shapefiles visit http://www.census.gov/geo/www/tiger</ordering></stdorder><techpreq>The TIGER/Line shapefiles contain geographic data only and do not include display mapping software or statistical data.  For information on how to use the TIGER/Line shapefile data with specific software package users shall contact the company that produced the software.</techpreq></distinfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>NJ Office of Information Technology (NJOIT), Office of Geographic Information Systems (OGIS)</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing address</addrtype><address>PO Box 212</address><city>Trenton</city><state>NJ</state><postal>08625-0212</postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>609.633.9103</cntvoice><cntemail>njgin@oit.state.nj.us</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>Downloadable Data</resdesc><distliab>The State of New Jersey provides the data set "as is". The State makes no guarantee or warranty concerning the accuracy of information contained in the data. Also, the State makes no warranty, either expressed or implied, regarding the condition of the product or its fitness for any particular purpose. The burden for determining fitness for use lies entirely with the user. Although these data files have been processed successfully on computers at the State, no warranty is made by the State regarding the use of the data on any other system, nor does the fact of distribution constitute or imply such a warranty.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>AVSHP</formname><formverd>2013</formverd><filedec>ZIP (Windows)</filedec></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://njgin.state.nj.us/NJ_NJGINExplorer/DataDownloads.jsp</networkr><networkr>https://njgin.state.nj.us/oit/gis/download/Census2010Blk.zip</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>none</fees><ordering>
Shapefile in NAD83 NJ State Plane feet can be downloaded from NJGIN data download Web page.

Data in geographic coordinates can be obtained directly from the U.S. Census Bureau TIGER Web site.
</ordering></stdorder><availabl><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>201307</begdate><enddate>present</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo></availabl></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20130719</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>NJ Office of Information Technology (NJOIT), Office of Geographic Information Systems (OGIS)</cntorg><cntper>Edith Konopka</cntper></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing address</addrtype><address>PO Box 212</address><city>Trenton</city><state>NJ</state><postal>08625-0212</postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>609.777.3774</cntvoice><cntemail>edith.konopka@oit.state.nj.us</cntemail><cntinst>
Original metadata content from: U.S. Department of Commerce, U.S. Census Bureau, Geography Division, Geographic Products Branch
voice 301-763-1128
fax 301-763-4710
geo.tiger@census.gov
mail 4600 Silver Hill Road, Stop 7400
Washington, DC 20233-7400
USA
</cntinst></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo><Esri><CreaDate>20170427</CreaDate><CreaTime>19324800</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><ArcGISstyle>North American Profile of ISO19115 2003</ArcGISstyle><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce></Esri></metadata>
